ZACHARY XENITOPOULOS

zacxfitness@gmail.com · 0402 377292

An eager professional with a high interest and knowledge in business relations and customer service, educational training and Office 365. I am equally capable of working with big teams and independently to meet goals and KPI's, whilst working under pressure to meet deadline-based tasks. I have developed a great knowledge and understanding of - Microsoft Office 365 (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), Member Management Systems, SharePoint/teams sites and document management with over five years of experience. My skills have allowed me to educate and train others with effective, clear and precise knowledge to a wide range of individuals and levels of competency. I embrace new challenges and thrive under challenging situations.

EXPERIENCE

JANURARY 2023- CURRENT

SUB BRANCH KNOWLEDGE INFORMATION PORTAL ADMINISTRATOR (SHAREPOINT)

- Collaborate with a wide range of stakeholders to create and develop content for SharePoint Intranet and communication sites.
- Design modern web pages to capture targeted audiences and convey information in a clear and detailed manner.
- Implement changes to SharePoint sites which engage end users and match the businesses goals and objectives.
- Auditing and managing SharePoint data and documents.
- Collaborate with SharePoint architects to develop PowerApps and new initiatives.
- Build Power Automate flows, Develop PowerBi reports, MS Visio and training manuals.
- Provide SharePoint training to 10 Districts across Queensland and 200+ Sub Branches.
- Use of Azure Devops for new development and technical issues.

SEPTEMBER 2022 – JANURARY 2023

MEMBERSHIP SERVICE COORDINATOR, RSL QLD

- Deliver training on IT managed systems such as MMS, SKIP and SharePoint to a wide range of audiences
- Collaborate with key stakeholders to obtain feedback and areas for improvement
- Creating content for SKIP in multiple formats
- Contribute to ongoing development of management systems and digital functionality whilst briefing new features and improvements to stakeholders
- Generating reports and analysing data
- Weekly and monthly reporting to key stakeholders
- Grow and maintain RSL membership data base
- · Communicating effectively with Sub Branches and District Presidents/Secretaries to identify areas of improvement

2020 - August 2021

CONTRACTS ADMINISTRATOR, ASP PILING PTY LTD

- Engaging, managing, reviewing and amending high profile contractual agreements and negotiations
- Working with key business stakeholders to process tender offers and retention payments
- Collaborating with safety and compliance officers on OH&S/SWIMS agreements
- Upkeep and maintenance of internal record documents
- Internal reporting on financial and contractual data
- Manage Microsoft office live documents for managing regarding contractual progression
- Collaborating with external lawyers on a wide range of construction matters

2018 - 2020

TEAM LEADER, GLOBAL INTERACTIVE

- Responsible for the oversite of 10-15 sales associates
- Manage, develop and present training criteria to sales associates and further stakeholders within the business
- Conduct management plans for under performing individuals
- Collaborating with the CFO and CEO on business development and improvements
- Responsible for day to day operations of high profile marketing agreements with a wide range of charity organisations
- Weekly and monthly reporting on team statistics
- Upkeep and maintain storage and digital documents via Excel and SharePoint

2015 - 2018

PERSONAL TRAINER, GOODLIFE HEALTH CLUBS

- Develop training plans and group fitness class schedules
- Retaining and growing new client portfolios
- Managing outgoing costs and business finances
- Working with management to develop progression plans for growth and development

EDUCATION

- Business Diploma, Careers Australia
- SharePoint Basics, Odyssey Training
- SharePoint Advanced, Odyssey Training
- PowerBI Reporting, Odyssey Training
- First Aid & Mental Heath First Aid, Saint Johns Ambulance
- Advanced Diploma in IT (Full-Stack Bootcamp), Coder Academy (Ongoing)